inlappseo.com 2016-01-23

# Inlapp SEO Services - About Us

We, at InlappSEO.com, are enthusiastic to give you an exciting and pleasurable online experience at all times. Once at our site we treat you as an important person by giving you service that is worthy of a king. To ensure this, we have listed the components of our Privacy Policy below:

**Use of Personal Information**

Personal information at our website is used for the sole purposes intended and is held confidentially. This means that without your permission it will never be used for any other purposes other than the one we have agreed on.

The data that we collect automatically is only the one that is connected to our site. The data is unknown and collected through log files in our servers. These files gather only information concerning the count and type of visitors our site receives but it will never collect any data that is personal. It is in this way that we get information on how to improve the preferences of our viewer’s.

**Use of Cookies**

Some of our pages use a feature of your browser called a "cookie". Cookies do not extract any personal information from you. What a cookie does is that it only identifies information about your computer but not you. Therefore, no one at InlappSEO.com will ever know your identity even after we assign your computer a cookie.

These cookies are helpful in making our website personalized according to your preferences. For example - When your product is registered online, your computer is assigned a cookie that will help you get the support you need, without retyping any information.

**Contact Us**

InlappSEO.com is very keen on maintaining your privacy. You can send your queries and comments regarding our privacy policy to [contact@inlappseo.com](mailto:contact@inlappseo.com). Due to the rapid change in internet technology, InlappSEO.com reserves the right to change its privacy policy from time to time.

Copyright © 2009 All Rights Reserved. Inlapp SEO Services is a part of [Inlapp](http://www.inlapp.com/).
